Guide to the American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), District Council 1707 Records WAG.298
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series III: Agency Files, 1947-2007
  - Bank Street College of Education: Bargaining (Local 253), 1980-1986 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Bank Street College of Education: Bargaining (Local 253), 1988-1998 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Bank Street College of Education: Bargaining (Local 253), 2000-2007 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Bank Street College of Education: Grievances (Local 253), 1995-2000 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Belle and Samuel Rose YM-YWHA of Southern Westchester: Bargaining (Local 253), 1996 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Belle and Samuel Rose YM-YWHA of Southern Westchester: Grievances (Local 253), 1994-1999 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Belle and Samuel Rose YM-YWHA of Southern Westchester: Personnel, General Administrative (Local 253), 1994-1998 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - B'Nai B'Rith International/B'Nai B'Rith Youth Organization: Bargaining (Local 107), 1989-1996 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Board of Jewish Education: Bargaining (Local 253), 1948-1975 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Board of Jewish Education: Bargaining (Local 253), 1975-1989 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Board of Jewish Education: Bargaining (Local 253), 1990-2005 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Board of Jewish Education: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 253), 1995 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Boro Park YM and YWHA Senior Center: Bargaining (Local 215), 1996 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Boro Park YM and YWHA Senior Center: Grievance--Chaim Nachman (Local 215), 1999 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Boro Park YM and YWHA Senior Center: Personnel (Local 215) (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Bowery Residents Committee (BRC) Human Services Corporation: Bargaining (Local 215), 1991-1997 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Bowery Residents Committee (BRC) Human Services Corporation: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 215), 1996 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Bowery Residents Committee (BRC) Human Services Corporation: Grievances (Local 215), 1999 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Bronx House Jewish Community Center: Bargaining (Local 215), 1996 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Bronx House Jewish Community Center: Grievances/Personnel Issues (Local 215), 1994-1998 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Bronx House Jewish Community Center: Grievances--Teachers Vacation (Local 215), 1994-1996 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Bronx House Jewish Community Center: Grievance--Davis, Hernowitz, and Nadel (Local 215), 1996-1999 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Bushwick Economic Development Vendor Agency: Bargaining (Local 389), 2001 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - [Center for Employment Opportunities?] (CEO): General Administrative, 1998 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Central Queens YM-YWHA: Bargaining (Local 215), 1975, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Central Queens YM-YWHA: Grievances (Local 215), 1994-1998 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Central Queens YM-YWHA: Grievance--Myron Fulton (Local 215), 1993-1998 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Central Queens YM-YWHA: Personnel (Local 215), 1994-1999, undated (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Children's Aid Society: Election Materials, Feb 1998 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Children's Corner Day Care Center, Inc.: Bargaining [Local 205], [1996] (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Concourse House: Personnel Policy Manual, [1998] (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Consortium for Worker Education (CWE): Wage Subsidy Program, 2002, undated (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Council of Jewish Federations (CJF): Bargaining (Local 107), 1995-1999 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Council of Jewish Federations (CJF): Merger with United Jewish Appeal (Local 107), 1998-1999 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Council of Jewish Federations (CJF): Personnel (Local 107), 1997-1999 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Development Corporation for Israel: Bargaining (Local 107, Local 1881), 1953-1962 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Development Corporation for Israel: Bargaining (Local 107, Local 1881), 1963-1967 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Development Corporation for Israel: Bargaining (Local 107, Local 1881), 1969-1975 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Development Corporation for Israel: Bargaining (Local 107, Local 1881), 1976-[1981] (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Development Corporation for Israel: Bargaining (Local 107, Local 1881), [1983]-1987 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Development Corporation for Israel: Bargaining (Local 107, Local 1881), [1989]-[1994] (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Development Corporation for Israel: Bargaining (Local 107, Local 1881), 1994-1999 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Development Corporation for Israel: General Administrative/Personnel (Local 107, Local 1881), 1999-2000 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Development Corporation for Israel: Grievances (Local 107, Local 1881), 1995-2000 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Development Corporation for Israel: Grievances (Local 107, Local 1881), 1996-1997 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - District Council 1707 Professional Employees Union: Bargaining, 1977-1993 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - District Council 1707 Professional Employees Union: Bargaining, 1977-1997 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - East New York YM and YWHA: Bargaining, 1956-[1963] (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - East Tremont YM and YWHA: Bargaining, 1954-1956 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Educational Alliance: Bargaining (Local 215), [1991]-1997 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Educational Alliance: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 215), 1995-1997 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Educational Alliance: Grievance (Local 215), 1955 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - HR Dynamics, Inc. (FEGS and NYANA): General Administrative, Grievances (Local 215), 2000, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Family Service Society of Yonkers: Bargaining (Local 389), 1998-[2001] (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEG) [Federation Employment Service]: Bargaining (Local 215), [1950]-1953 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Bargaining (Local 215), 1955-1962 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Bargaining (Local 215), 1964-1975 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Bargaining (Local 215), 1977-1981 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Bargaining (Local 215), 1981-1983 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Bargaining (Local 215), 1985-1988 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Bargaining (Local 215), 1988-1989 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Bargaining (Local 215), 1990-1999 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Bargaining (Local 215), 2000 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): DC 1707 Staff Representative Files; General Administrative (Local 215), 1995-1996 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Flyers (Local 215), [1996-1999] (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Grievances (Local 215), 1994-1996 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Grievances (Local 215), 1994-1997 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Grievances (Local 215), 1995-1996 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Grievances (Local 215), 1997 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Grievances (Local 215), 1998-1999 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Grievances (Local 215), 2000-2001 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Grievances--Mike Davis, Donald Monaco (Local 215), 1985-1995 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Grievance--George Goldson (Local 215), 1990-1995 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Grievance--Jannie Terry (Local 215), 1996-1997 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Personnel/General Administrative (Local 215), 1995-1997 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Personnel--Layoff Notices (Local 215), 1995 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Personnel--Layoff Notices (Local 215), 1995 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Personnel--Layoff Notices (Local 215), 1996 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Federation Employment and Guidance Service (FEGS): Personnel--Layoff Notices (Local 215), 1997 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Federation Group Work Agencies: Bargaining (Local 215), 1956-1963 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Federation Group Work Agencies: Bargaining (Local 215), 1965-2000 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Federation Group Work Agencies: Bargaining (Local 215), 1968-1975 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Federation Group Work Agencies: Bargaining (Local 215), 1971-1988 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Federation Group Work Agencies: Bargaining (Local 215), 1977-1988 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Federation Group Work Agencies: Bargaining (Local 215), 1993-1999 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Federation Group Work Agencies: Bargaining (Local 215), 1994-1997 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Federation Group Work Agencies: Bargaining (Local 215), 1996-1998 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Federation Group Work Agencies: Bargaining (Local 215), 1999-2000 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Federation Group Work Agencies: Bargaining (Local 215), 2006 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Federation Group Work Agencies: General Administrative, Grievances (Local 215), 1992-2000 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Federation Group Work Agencies: Grievances (Local 215), 1992-1999 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies (FOJP) Service Corporation: Bargaining (Local 107), 1979-1981 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies (FOJP) Service Corporation: Bargaining (Local 107), 1984-1988 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies (FOJP) Service Corporation: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files, General Administrative (Local 107), 1994-1998 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies (FOJP) Service Corporation: Grievances (I) (Local 107), 1994-2000 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies (FOJP) Service Corporation: Grievances (II) (Local 107), 1994-2000 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies (FOJP) Service Corporation: Grievances--Sonia Flanagan (Local 107), 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies (FOJP) Service Corporation: Grievances--Arnold Grab (Local 107), 1994-1997 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies (FOJP) Service Corporation: Grievances--Nanette Norwood (Local 107), 1993-1994 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies (FOJP) Service Corporation: Grievances--Gaetana J. Vega (Local 107), 1989-1997 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies (FOJP) Service Corporation: Personnel--Monthly Reports (Local 107), 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies (FOJP) Service Corporation: Personnel--Monthly Reports (Local 107), 1995 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies (FOJP) Service Corporation: Personnel--Monthly Reports (Local 107), 1996 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies (FOJP) Service Corporation: Personnel--Monthly Reports (Local 107), 1997 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies (FOJP) Service Corporation: Personnel--Monthly Reports (Local 107) (I), 1998 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies (FOJP) Service Corporation: Personnel--Monthly Reports (Local 107) (II), 1998 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies (FOJP) Service Corporation: Personnel--Monthly Reports (Local 107), 1999-2000 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Federation of the Handicapped: Organizing Campaign(Local 389), 1990, undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Ferncliff Manor for the Retarded: Bargaining--Unfair Labor Practices, 1995-1999 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Ferncliff Manor for the Retarded: Bargaining--Unfair Labor Practices, 1997-1999 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Ferncliff Manor for the Retarded: Bargaining--Unfair Labor Practices (NLRB Case), 1997-1999 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Fountain House: Grievances, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - GHI Home Care Services: Bargaining (Local 389), 1983-1989 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - GHI Home Health Homemaker Services: Bargaining (Local 389), 1979 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Grand Street Settlement: Bargaining (DC 1707 Staff Representative Files)(Local 107), 1995-1996 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Gustave Hartman YM and YWHA: General Administrative, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Hadassah: Bargaining (Local 107), 1950-1959 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Hadassah: Bargaining (Local 107), 1960-1968 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Hadassah: Bargaining/DC 1707 Staff Representative File (Local 107), 1992-1995 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Hale House Center: Bargaining (Local 215), 2005 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Hebrew Educational Society: Bargaining (Local 215), 1971, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Hebrew Educational Society: Bargaining (Local 215), 1995-1996 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Hebrew Educational Society: Grievances (Local 215), 1995-1997 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Hebrew Educational Society: Personnel (Local 215), 1994-2000 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Hebrew Immigrant Aid Society (HIAS): Bargaining (Local 215), 1952-1959 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Hebrew Immigrant Aid Society (HIAS): Bargaining (Local 215), 1961-1978 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Hebrew Immigrant Aid Society (HIAS): Bargaining (Local 215), 1980-1982 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Hebrew Immigrant Aid Society (HIAS): Bargaining (Local 215), 1986-1990 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Hebrew Immigrant Aid Society (HIAS): Bargaining (Local 215), 1992 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Hebrew Immigrant Aid Society (HIAS): Bargaining (Local 215), 1994-1995 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Hebrew Immigrant Aid Society (HIAS): Bargaining (Local 215), 1994-1995 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Hebrew Immigrant Aid Society (HIAS): Bargaining (Local 215), 1998-2002 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Hebrew Immigrant Aid Society (HIAS): Bargaining (Local 215), 2007 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Hebrew Immigrant Aid Society (HIAS): Ephemera (Local 215), Undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Hebrew Immigrant Aid Society (HIAS): General Administrative (Local 215), [1968] (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Hebrew Immigrant Aid Society (HIAS): Personnel/Grievances (Local 215), 1994-1999 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Hebrew Immigrant Aid Society (HIAS): Personnel/Grievances (Local 215), 1995-1997 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Henry Street Settlement, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Highbridge Advisory Council: General Administrative, 1997-1998 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Home Assistance Personnel Inc.: Bargaining (Local 389), 1997-2000 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Home Attendant Vendor Agency, Inc. (HAVA): Bargaining (Local 389), 1984-[2001] (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Homes for the Homeless: Complaint Against DC 1707, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Hope House, Inc.: Organizing, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Hudson Guild: Bargaining (Local 215), 2006 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Huntington Freedom Center: Bargaining, Grievance (DC 1707 Staff Representative Files) (Local 253), 1995-1997 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Institute for Urban Family Health: Bargaining, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Institute of International Education: Bargaining. Grievances (DC 1707 Staff Representative Files) (Local 253), 1995-1997 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions: Bargaining, 1960-1968 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - International Rescue Committee: Bargaining (Local 215), 1950-1971 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - International Rescue Committee: Bargaining (Local 215), 1972-1988 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - International Rescue Committee: Bargaining (Local 215), 1990-2002 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - International Rescue Committee: Personnel, Grievances (Local 215), 1994-1997 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Jewish Association for Services for the Aged (JASA): Bargaining (Local 215), 1971-1983 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Jewish Association for Services for the Aged (JASA): Bargaining--Petitions (Local 215), Undated (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Jewish Association for Services for the Aged (JASA): DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 215), 1995-1997 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Jewish Board of Family and Children Services (JBFCS): Bargaining (Local 215), 1949-1958 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Jewish Board of Family and Children Services (JBFCS): Bargaining (Local 215), 1960-1973 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Jewish Board of Family and Children Services (JBFCS): Bargaining (Local 215) (Includes Joint Contracts with Jewish Child Care Association (JCCA)), 1975-1985 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Jewish Board of Family and Children Services (JBFCS): Bargaining (Local 215) (Includes Joint Contracts with Jewish Child Care Association (JCCA)), 1985-2001 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Jewish Board of Family and Children Services (JBFCS): Bargaining (Local 215) (Joint Contracts with Jewish Child Care Association (JCCA)) (I), 1993-1994 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Jewish Board of Family and Children Services (JBFCS): Bargaining (Local 215) (Joint Contracts with Jewish Child Care Association (JCCA)) (II), 1993-1994 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Jewish Board of Family and Children Services (JBFCS): Bargaining (Local 215), 1999 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Jewish Board of Family and Children Services (JBFCS): DC 1707 Staff Representatives Files (Local 215), 1995-1997 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Jewish Board of Family and Children Services (JBFCS): Grievances (Local 215), 1963-1995 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Jewish Care Services of Long Island, Inc.: Bargaining (Local 389), 1988-2000 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Jewish Child Care Association (JCCA): Bargaining (Local 215), 1971-2000 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Jewish Child Care Association (JCCA): DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 215), 1995-1997 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Jewish Child Care Association (JCCA): Grievance (Local 215), 1980 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Jewish Community Center of Metropolitan New Jersey/United Jewish Centers of MetroWest: Grievance--Arlene Safft (Local 215), 1994-1995 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Jewish Community Centers Association (JCC Association): Bargaining (Local 107), 1995 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Jewish Community Centers Association (JCC Association): Bargaining (Local 107), 1996-1999 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Jewish Community Centers Association (JCC Association): Bargaining (Local 107), 1996-2000 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Jewish Community Centers Association (JCC Association): DC 1707 Staff Representative Files/General Administrative (Local 107), 1995-2000 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Jewish Community Centers Association (JCC Association): Grievances (Local 107), 1998-2000 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Jewish Community Centers Association (JCC Association): Grievances (Local 107), 2000-2001 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Jewish Community Centers Association (JCC Association): Grievances--Madeleine Fante (Local 107), 1998-2000 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Jewish Community Centers Association (JCC Association): Grievances--re: Health Insurance Benefits (Local 107), 1998-2000 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Jewish Community Federation of Metropolitan New Jersey: Bargaining (Local 215), [1982] (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Jewish Community House of Bensonhurst: Bargaining/DC 1707 Staff Representative Files/General Administrative (Local 215), 1995-2000 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Jewish Community House of Bensonhurst: Grievance--Sofia Kabak (I) (Local 215), 1996-1998 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Jewish Community House of Bensonhurst: Grievance--Sofia Kabak (II) (Local 215), 1996-1998 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Jewish Community House of Bensonhurst: Grievance--Craig Wasserberg (Local 215), 1999-2000 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Jewish Community Services of Long Island: Bargaining (Local 215), 1980 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Jewish Council for Public Affairs (JCPA)[formerly National Jewish Community Relations Advisory Council (NJCRAC): Bargaining (Local 107), 1984-2000 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Jewish Council for Public Affairs (JCPA)[formerly National Jewish Community Relations Advisory Council (NJCRAC): Elections (Local 107), 1984 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Jewish Family Service: Bargaining (Local 215), 1954-1958 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Jewish Family Service: Bargaining (Local 215), 1960-1964 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Jewish Family Service: Bargaining (Local 215), 1966-1976 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Jewish Family Service: Grievances (Local 215), 1956-1961 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Jewish Family Service: Grievances (Local 215), 1961-1974 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Jewish National Fund: Bargaining (Local 107), 1947-1967 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Jewish National Fund: Bargaining (Local 107), 1970-1989 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Jewish National Fund: Bargaining (Local 107), 1989-2001 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Jewish National Fund: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files/General Administrative (Local 107), 1995-2000 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Jewish Theological Seminary: Bargaining/DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 253), 1995-1997 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Job Corps: General Administrative, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Joint Purchasing Corporation: Bargaining, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Kings Bay YM and YWHA: Bargaining/DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 215), 1996 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Kings Bay YM and YWHA: Personnel (Local 215), 1994-1999 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Leake and Watts: General Administrative, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Little Flower Children's Services: Bargaining, Grievance, General Adminstrative (Local 215), 1995-1999 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Living Resources Corporation: Election Petition, NLRB, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Long Island Head Start Child Development Services, Inc.: Bargaining, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Long Island Women's Coalition: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 253), 1995-1997 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Louise Wise Services: Bargaining (Local 215), 1956-1964 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Louise Wise Services: Bargaining (Local 215), 1967-1985 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Louise Wise Services: Bargaining (Local 215), 1987-1991 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Louise Wise Services: Bargaining (Local 215), 1992-2004 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Louise Wise Services: DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 215), 1995-1996 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Louise Wise Services: General Administrative (Local 215), 1994-1999 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Louise Wise Services: Grievances (Local 215), 1994-1999 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Louise Wise Services: Grievances (Local 215), 1994-1998 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Louise Wise Services: Grievances (Local 215), 1997-1999 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Louise Wise Services: Grievance--Idriys Muhammad (Local 215), 1998 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Louise Wise Services: Grievance--Sam Shortte (Local 215), 1996-2000 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Louise Wise Services: Grievance--Raquel Vasquez (Local 215), 1997-1999 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Lucille Murray Child Development: Grievances (Local 205), 1989 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Marriott Management Services: Grievances (Local 215), 1994-1997 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Metro Care Home Services: Unfair Labor Practices, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Metro North Day Care Center: Grievances (Local 205), 1989 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Miricle Makers, Inc.: NLRB Petition, Election Materials, 1998-1999, undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Mobilization for Youth: Bargaining, 1964-1965 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Mobilization for Youth: Bargaining, 1966-1974 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Mosholu Montefiore Community Center: Bargaining, DC 1707 Staff Representative Files (Local 215), 1991-1996 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Mosholu Montefiore Community Center: Personnel (Local 215), 1994-1999 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Mosholu Montefiore Community Center: Grievances (Local 215), 1988, 1992-1996 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) Legal Defense and Educational Fund: Bargaining (Local 107), 1951-1969 (Box 26, Folder 13)